<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tours>
  <tour>
    <tourId>01</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Cable Crunch</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. Grasp cable rope attachment and place wrist against the head while kneeling below a high pulley.

2. With the hips stationary, flex the waist so the elbows travel toward the middle of the thighs.. Return and repeat</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>02</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Cable Seated Crunch</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. Sit down with your back away from medium high pulley. Seize with both hands the cable robe attachment above your head. Place the securely over both shoulders.

2. Move the cable rope forward over your head. With the hips stationary, flex the waist so the elbows travel toward the hips. Repeat this. You can allow weights to make it harder for the lower back.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>03</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Decline Crunch</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdomainals</price>
    <description>
1. Sit straight up on an decline bench with your feet locked at the end. Start by holding your upper body raised off the bench. Place your hand behind your head. Don't hold your hands tight. Slowly lower your back. Don't go all the way down and touch the bench.
 
2. Raise your upper body slowly till you touch your elbows with your knees.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>04</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Decline Oblique Crunch</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. Sit straight up on an decline bench with your feet locked at the end. Start by holding your upper body raised off the bench. Place one hand behind your head and one holding your side upper leg. Don't hold your hands tight. Start by touching your right elbow with your left knee.

2. Slowly lower your back to a straight position, so your shoulders are horizontally. Don't go all the way down and touch the bench. Switch your sides while returning to your start position.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>05</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Decline Reverse Crunch</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. Lie on an decline bench with your arms up. Hold your legs horizontally. Keep your knees and feet together.

2. Slowly contract your abs and bring your legs to your chest. Let the abs do the working. Slowly return to the starting position.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>06</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Gorilla Chin/Chrunch</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals; Other muscle: Biceps, Lats.</price>
    <description>
1. Hang from a chinning bar with your knees bent and your hands slightly wider your shoulders. Chrunch your knees up. To make it harder you can pull yourself up at the same time. When fully contracted, your note will be at the bar and your knees will be pulled up to your chest. Return slowly to start position. </description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>07</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Hanging Knee Raise To The Side</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. Hang from a pull-up bar and keep your legs together. Slowly lift your knees and turn your body one side as high as you can go. 
2. Do this slowly while curling your spine from the bottom up. Try not to lift your knees only. Repeat and alternate sides. Do not swing your legs.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>08</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Hanging Leg Raise</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. Hang from a pull-up bar and keep your legs together straighten down. Raise your legs by flexing your hips while flexing your knees. Keep your hips fully flexed. Now raise your knees toward your shoulders by flexing your waist. Do not swing your legs up.
2. Slowly pull your legs up using your abs. To make it harder put an weight between your feet. Return and repeat.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>09</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Hanging Pike</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals.</price>
    <description>
1. Hang from a pull-up bar and keep your legs together straighten down. Keep your palms facing forward and place your arms somewhat wider than your shoulders. Start bending your knees till your upper legs are horizontally with the floor. 
2. Pull your shins to the pull.up bar and try to touch it. Don't swing back but try to slowly return to start position.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>10</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Knee/Hip Raise On Parallel Bars</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. This is a great exercise for the lower part of the abs. Keep in mind to use your abs to pull your legs up. Squeeze your abs at the top position.</description>
    <image>Abdominal</image>
</tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>11</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Ab Chrunch Machine</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Abdominals</price>
    <description>
1. Sit down in the machine and select a resistance that is with-in safe limits of your ability. Do a chrunch in a slow controlled manner while slowly breathing out. 
2.Pause at the bottom of your chrunch for 3 seconds. Return to your starting position in a slow controlled movement</description>
    <image>Abdominals</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>12</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Alternate Hammer Curl</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Biceps ; Other: Forearms</price>
    <description>
1. Stand straight up. Hold in each hand a dumbbell. Curl your right arm up. Your left arm is straight aside your body.
2. Curl your left arm and straighten your right arm aside your body. Repeat this but do only one arm at a time. </description>
    <image>biceps</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>13</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Barbell Curl</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Biceps</price>
    <description>
1. This is one of the best biceps exercises. Hold a bar at shoulder width and under hand grip.
2. Hold your elbows against your body. Raise the bar until your forearms are almost vertical. Lower again till your arms are almost fully extended. </description>
    <image>biceps</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>14</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Cable Hammer Curls - Rope </tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Biceps</price>
    <description>
1. Hold a rope that is attached to a low pulley. Place your feet at shoulder with your arms down and your palms facing each other. Keep your elbows locked to your side.
2. Pull your arms toward your shoulder until your forearms touches your biceps. Slowly return to the starting position and repeat.</description>
    <image>biceps</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>15</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Kneeling Cable Concentration Triceps Extension</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Triceps</price>
    <description>
1.With your right hand hold a stirrup handle that is connected to a high pulley. Face your left side towards the machine and kneel down onto your left knee. Keep your right knee bent and your upper thigh parallel to the floor. Your right elbow and upper arm should be kept against the inner thigh at all times.
2. In a semicircular motion move your arm down intil it is vertical and your elbow is locked. Slowly return to the starting position.</description>
    <image>Triceps</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>16</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Machine Preacher Curls</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Biceps</price>
    <description>
1. Sit down behind the pulley. Hold the handles in your hands.
2. Curl your arms towards your chest. Than slowly curl back. Repeat this. </description>
    <image>biceps</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>17</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Overhead Cable Curl</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Biceps</price>
    <description>
1. Before starting attach the stirrup to two overhead cable pulleys. Put the handles in your hands and stand in the middle of it. Hold your arms straight, just like the letter T.
2. Curl your hands toward your shoulders. It is important that your elbows should not go up or down, and they must not go forward. hold it for 3-5 seconds and return to the starting position.</description>
    <image>biceps</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>18</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Seated Bent-Over One-Arm kickback</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Triceps</price>
    <description>
1. Sit on a bench and hold a dumbbell in your hand keeping your lower arm vertical and upper arm to your side.
2. Press the dumbbell slowly back until you have straighten your arm parallel to the floor. Lower slowly and switch arms.</description>
    <image>triceps</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>19</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Standing Low-Pulley One-Arm Triceps Extension</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Triceps</price>
    <description>
1. Hold the handle of the low pulley in your left hand behind your head and put your right hand on your left elbow to stabilize.
2. Keep your elbow close to your head and straighten your lower arm. Switch arms.</description>
    <image>Triceps</image>
</tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>20</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Dip Machine</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Triceps</price>
    <description>
1. Sit securely in a dip machine, select the weight and firmly grasp the handles. Now keep your elbows in at your sides in order to place emphasis on the triceps. The elbows should be bent at a 90 degree angle. 
2. As you contract the triceps, extend your arms downwards as you exhale. Tip: At the bottom of the movement, focus on keeping a little bend in your arms to keep tension on the triceps muscle. Now slowly let your arms come back up to the starting position as you inhale.
</description>
    <image>Triceps</image>

  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>21</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Bent Over Barbell Row</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Middle Back ; Other: Biceps, Lats, Triceps</price>
    <description>
1. Hold a bar with hands a little wider than shoulder width while bending over, So your back is as close to parallel to the floor as you can and put your feet at about shoulder width.
2. Pull the bar straight up to your chest and slowly lower the bar back to the starting position while keeping your head up and back straight.</description>
    <image>Middle Back</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>22</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Lying T-bar Row</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Middle Back</price>
    <description>
1. Load up the T-bar Row Machine with the desired weight and adjust the leg height so that your upper chest is at the top of the pad. Lay face down on the pad and grab the handles. You can either use a palms down, palms up, or palms in position depending on what part of your back you want to emphasize. Lift the bar off the rack and extend your arms in front of you. This will be your starting position. 
2. As you exhale slowly pull the weight up and squeeze your back at the top of the movement. Tip: Keep the upper arms as close to the torso as possible throughout the movement in order to better engage the back muscles. Also, do not lift your body off of the pad at any time and refrain from using the biceps to lift the weight.
</description>
    <image>back</image>
	</tour>
  	<tour>
<tourId>23</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Close-Grip Front Lat Pulldown</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Lats</price>
    <description>
1.This exercise is for the lower lats. Sit at a pulldown machine and lock your knees under the pads. Hold the lat bar at less than shoulder width with your palm facing forwards.
2. Pull the bar straight to the floor till it touches your chest. Slowly return and repeat.</description>
    <image>back</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>24</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Elevated Cable Rows</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Lats</price>
    <description>
1. Sit straight on the cable row machine. Lean forward with a strong arch in your back. Get the handles with your palms facing each other.
2. Pull the handles towards your abs. Keep your body vertically and don't lean back.</description>
    <image>back</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>25</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Middle Back Shrug</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Middle Back; Other: Shoulders, Lats, Traps</price>
    <description>
1. Grab two dumbbells when lying face own on a bench.
2. Squeeze your shoulder blades together and hold the concentration for a full second. This exercise hits the upper back muscles. </description>
    <image>back</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>26</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Pullups</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Lats ; Other: Biceps, Middle Back</price>
    <description>
1. Begin holding the pull-up bar. Hold on to an overhand grip twice the shoulder width. Straighten your arms. let your body hang from the bar and keep your legs straight.
2. Pull yourself uo to the bar so that the top of your chest almost touches the bar and your chin is over the bar. Hold your body straight. To make it harder, add a weight or to make it easier get someone to lift your legs. Return to start position. </description>
    <image>back</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <tourId>27</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Leverage Iso Row</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Lats</price>
    <description>
1. Load an appropriate weight onto the pins and adjust the seat height so that the handles are at chest level. Grasp the handles with either a neutral or pronated grip. This will be your starting position. 
2. Pull the handles towards your torso, retracting your shoulder blades as you flex the elbow. Pause at the bottom of the motion, and then slowly return the handles to the starting position. For multiple repetitions, avoid completely returning the weight to the stops to keep tension on the muscles being worked
</description>
    <image>back</image>
  </tour>
<tour>
<tourId>28</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Butterfly</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Chest</price>
    <description>
1. Sit on the machine with your back flat on the pad. Take hold of the handles. Tip: Your upper arms should be positioned parallel to the floor; adjust the machine accordingly. This will be your starting position. 
2. Push the handles together slowly as you squeeze your chest in the middle. Breathe out during this part of the motion and hold the contraction for a second. Return back to the starting position slowly as you inhale until your chest muscles are fully stretched.
 </description>
    <image>chest</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>29</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Decline Smith Press</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Chest</price>
    <description>
1. Place a decline bench underneath the Smith machine. Now place the barbell at a height that you can reach when lying down and your arms are almost fully extended. Using a pronated grip that is wider than shoulder width, unlock the bar from the rack and hold it straight over you with your arms extended. This will be your starting position. 
2. As you inhale, lower the bar under control by allowing the elbows to flex, lightly contacting the torso. After a brief pause, bring the bar back to the starting position by extending the elbows, exhaling as you do so. 
</description>
    <image>chest</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>30</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Cable Chest Press</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Chest</price>
    <description>
1. Adjust the weight to an appropriate amount and be seated, grasping the handles. Your upper arms should be about 45 degrees to the body, with your head and chest up. The elbows should be bent to about 90 degrees. This will be your starting position. 
2. Begin by extending through the elbow, pressing the handles together straight in front of you. Keep your shoulder blades retracted as you execute the movement. After pausing at full extension, return to th starting position, keeping tension on the cables.
. </description>
    <image>chest</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>31</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Cable Crossover</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Chest</price>
    <description>
1. To get yourself into the starting position, place the pulleys on a high position (above your head), select the resistance to be used and hold the pulleys in each hand. Step forward in front of an imaginary straight line between both pulleys while pulling your arms together in front of you. Your torso should have a small forward bend from the waist. This will be your starting position. 
2. With a slight bend on your elbows in order to prevent stress at the biceps tendon, extend your arms to the side (straight out at both sides) in a wide arc until you feel a stretch on your chest. Breathe in as you perform this portion of the movement. Tip: Keep in mind that throughout the movement, the arms and torso should remain stationary; the movement should only occur at the shoulder joint. Return your arms back to the starting position as you breathe out. Make sure to use the same arc of motion used to lower the weights.
 </description>
    <image>Chest</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>32</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Barbell Squat</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Quadriceps</price>
    <description>
1. To begin, first set the bar on a rack to just below shoulder level. Once the correct height is chosen and the bar is loaded, step under the bar and place the back of your shoulders (slightly below the neck) across it. Hold on to the bar using both arms at each side and lift it off the rack by first pushing with your legs and at the same time straightening your torso. Step away from the rack and position your legs using a shoulder width medium stance with the toes slightly pointed out. Keep your head up at all times and also maintain a straight back. This will be your starting position. 
2. Begin to slowly lower the bar by bending the knees and hips as you maintain a straight posture with the head up. Continue down until the angle between the upper leg and the calves becomes slightly less than 90-degrees. Inhale as you perform this portion of the movement. Slowly raise the bar as you exhale by pushing the floor with the heel of your foot as you straighten the legs again and go back to the starting position.
</description>
    <image>Leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>33</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Bycycling, Stationary</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Quadriceps</price>
    <description>
1. To begin, seat yourself on the bike and adjust the seat to your height. 
2. Select the desired option from the menu. You may have to start pedaling to turn it on. You can use the manual setting, or you can select a program to use. Typically, you can enter your age and weight to estimate the amount of calories burned during exercise. The level of resistance can be changed throughout the workout. The handles can be used to monitor your heart rate to help you stay at an appropriate intensity.
</description>
    <image>leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>34</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Cable Hip Adduction</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Quadriceps</price>
    <description>
1. Stand in front of a low pulley facing forward with one leg next to the pulley and the other one away. Attach the ankle cuff to the cable and also to the ankle of the leg that is next to the pulley. Now step out and away from the stack with a wide stance and grasp the bar of the pulley system. Stand on the foot that does not have the ankle cuff (the far foot) and allow the leg with the cuff to be pulled towards the low pulley. This will be your starting position. 
2. Now perform the movement by moving the leg with the ankle cuff in front of the far leg by using the inner thighs to abduct the hip. Breathe out during this portion of the movement. Slowly return to the starting position as you breathe in.
</description>
    <image>leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>35</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Leg Extensions</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Quadriceps</price>
    <description>
1. For this exercise you will need to use a leg extension machine. First choose your weight and sit on the machine with your legs under the pad (feet pointed forward) and the hands holding the side bars. This will be your starting position. Make sure that your legs form a 90-degree angle between the lower and upper leg. If the angle is less than 90-degrees then that means the knee is over the toes which in turn creates undue stress at the knee joint. If the machine is designed that way, either look for another machine or just make sure that when you start executing the exercise you stop going down once you hit the 90-degree angle.
2. Using your quadriceps, extend your legs to the maximum as you exhale. Ensure that the rest of the body remains stationary on the seat. Pause a second on the contracted position. Slowly lower the weight back to the original position as you inhale, ensuring that you do not go past the 90-degree angle limit.
</description>
    <image>Leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>36</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Leg Press</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Quadriceps</price>
    <description>
1. Using a leg press machine, sit down on the machine and place your legs on the platform directly in front of you at a medium (shoulder width) foot stance. Lower the safety bars holding the weighted platform in place and press the platform all the way up until your legs are fully extended in front of you. Tip: Make sure that you do not lock your knees. Your torso and the legs should make a perfect 90-degree angle. This will be your starting position. 
2. As you inhale, slowly lower the platform until your upper and lower legs make a 90-degree angle. Pushing mainly with the heels of your feet and using the quadriceps go back to the starting position as you exhale
</description>
    <image>leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>37</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Lying Leg Curls</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Hamstrings</price>
    <description>
1. Adjust the machine lever to fit your height and lie face down on the leg curl machine with the pad of the lever on the back of your legs (just a few inches under the calves). Tip: Preferably use a leg curl machine that is angled as opposed to flat since an angled position is more favorable for hamstrings recruitment. Keeping the torso flat on the bench, ensure your legs are fully stretched and grab the side handles of the machine. 
2. Position your toes straight (or you can also use any of the other two stances described on the foot positioning section). This will be your starting position. As you exhale, curl your legs up as far as possible without lifting the upper legs from the pad. Once you hit the fully contracted position, hold it for a second. As you inhale, bring the legs back to the initial position
</description>
    <image>leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>38</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Seated Leg Curl</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Hamstrings</price>
    <description>
1. Adjust the machine lever to fit your height and sit on the machine with your back against the back support pad. Place the back of lower leg on top of padded lever (just a few inches under the calves) and secure the lap pad against your thighs, just above the knees. Then grasp the side handles on the machine as you point your toes straight (or you can also use any of the other two stances) and ensure that the legs are fully straight right in front of you. This will be your starting position. 
2. As you exhale, pull the machine lever as far as possible to the back of your thighs by flexing at the knees. Keep your torso stationary at all times. Hold the contracted position for a second.
</description>
    <image>leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>39</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Standing Leg Curl</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Hamstrings</price>
    <description>
1. Adjust the machine lever to fit your height and lie with your torso bent at the waist facing forward around 30-45 degrees (since an angled position is more favorable for hamstrings recruitment) with the pad of the lever on the back of your right leg (just a few inches under the calves) and the front of the right leg on top of the machine pad. Keeping the torso bent forward, ensure your leg is fully stretched and grab the side handles of the machine. Position your toes straight. This will be your starting position. 
2. As you exhale, curl your right leg up as far as possible without lifting the upper leg from the pad. Once you hit the fully contracted position, hold it for a second. As you inhale, bring the legs back to the initial position.
</description>
    <image>leg</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>40</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Alternating Cable Shoulder Press</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Shoulder</price>
    <description>
1. Move the cables to the bottom of the tower and select an appropriate weight. Grasp the cables and hold them at shoulder height, palms facing forward. This will be your starting position. 
2. Keeping your head and chest up, extend through the elbow to press one side directly over head. After pausing at the top, return to the starting position and repeat on the opposite side. 
</description>
    <image>shoulder</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>41</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Barbell Incline Shoulder Raise</tourTitle>
    <description>
1. Lie back on an Incline Bench. Using a medium width grip (a grip that is slightly wider than shoulder width), lift the bar from the rack and hold it straight over you with your arms straight. This will be your starting position. 
2. While keeping the arms straight, lift the bar by protracting your shoulder blades, raising the shoulders from the bench as you breathe out. Bring back the bar to the starting position as you breathe in.
</description>
    <price>Main Muscle: Shoulder</price>
    <image>shoulder</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>42</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Cable Rear Delt Fly</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Shoulders</price>
    <description>
1. Adjust the pulleys to the appropriate height and adjust the weight. The pulleys should be above your head. Grab the left pulley with your right hand and the right pulley with your left hand, crossing them in front of you. This will be your starting position. 
2. Initiate the movement by moving your arms back and outward, keeping your arms straight as you execute the movement. Pause at the end of the motion before returning the handles to the start position. 
</description>
    <image>shoulder</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>43</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Leverage Shoulder Press</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: Shoulder</price>
    <description>
1. Load an appropriate weight onto the pins and adjust the seat for your height. The handles should be near the top of the shoulders at the beginning of the motion. Your chest and head should be up and handles held with a pronated grip. This will be your starting position. 
2. Press the handles upward by extending through the elbow. After a brief pause at the top, return the weight to just above the start position, keeping tension on the muscles by not returning the weight to the stops until the set is complete. 
</description>
    <image>shoulder</image>
  </tour>
  <tour>
<tourId>44</tourId>
    <tourTitle>Reverse Machine Flyes</tourTitle>
    <price>Main Muscle: shoulder</price>
    <description>
1. Adjust the handles so that they are fully to the rear. Make an appropriate weight selection and adjust the seat height so the handles are at shoulder level. Grasp the handles with your hands facing inwards. This will be your starting position. 
2. In a semicircular motion, pull your hands out to your side and back, contracting your rear delts. Keep your arms slightly bent throughout the movement, with all of the motion occurring at the shoulder joint. Pause at the rear of the movement, and slowly return the weight to the starting position. 
</description>
    <image>shoulder</image>
   </tour>
  </tours>

